dropshippingwholesalers.com 2009-06-17

# Drop Shipping Wholesale Resources from Drop Shipping Wholesalers - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy/Earnings Disclaimer**  

DropShippingWholesalers.com values the privacy of our visitors/customers and takes every known precaution to safe guard the information we collect from unauthorized use. The following is a detailed explanation of the privacy policy for DropShippingWholesalers.com. 

Information We Collect

DropShippingWholesalers.com believes it is important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site to join as a member. When you become a member of our site by purchasing a plan, we ask for your full name, address, telephone number, and credit card, checking, or PayPal information to process your order.  All of this information remains strictly confidential and will not be used or sold to another third party.

Why Do We Collect This Information?

We use this information in order to serve the needs of our customers. We need to know who you are in order to verify the credit card, checking, or PayPal information you have sent us. 

How is Your Information Protected?

We use the latest in encryption technology, including 256 bit SSL encryption to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception. We employ the latest in firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our members areas. Passwords are required in order for you to gain access to your account. Once an account has been terminated, measures are taken to remove those users from the system who no longer need access to our system. 

Notice of Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented. We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes.

DISCLAIMER

DropShippingWholesalers.com is not in the business of providing consulting or legal services and we recommend that you speak to a consultant or an attorney before relying on this privacy policy for your own use. While we do not think a privacy policy is a legal document, we feel it is a good idea to have a third-party such as a consultant or an attorney review your policy before you begin to implement it on your site. The privacy policy above should not be construed as the rendering of any business or legal advice. 

**EARNINGS DISCLAIMER**

We make every effort to ensure that we accurately represent the products and services and their potential for income. Earning statements made by our company and its customers are estimates of what we think you can possibly earn. There is no guarantee that you will make these levels of income and you accept the risk that the earnings and income statements differ by individual.

As with any business, your results may vary, and will be based on your individual capacity, business experience, expertise, and level of desire. There are no guarantees concerning the level of success you may experience. The testimonials and examples used are exceptional results, which do not apply to the average purchaser, and are not intended to represent or guarantee that anyone will achieve the same or similar results. Each individual’s success depends on his or her background, dedication, desire and motivation.

There is no assurance that examples of earnings can be duplicated in the future. We cannot guarantee your future results and/or success. There are some unknown risks in business. We are not responsible for your actions.

The use of our information, products and services should be based on your own due diligence and you agree that our company is not liable for any success or failure of your business that is directly or indirectly related to the purchase and use of our information, products and services.

The examples of products on our page are examples and should be reviewed and confirmed by the individual who wishes to sell them.  

* * *
